so hello everybody let's talk about
所以大家好，我们来谈谈
scaling up with luck for algorithms
运气好的算法
today so I let me present myself I and
今天，让我介绍自己，我和
therefore the things interesting here I
因此，这里有趣的事情
teach concurrent I serve you as a
教并发，我为您服务
program in a st. Petersburg IT mo but
程序在圣。彼得斯堡IT但是
we're not going to go into deep theory
我们不会去深入理论
of concurrent computing today today
今天的并发计算
we're going to talk about scalability
我们将讨论可伸缩性
issues and what we'll see some some some
问题，我们将看到一些
stuff I also work in Kaplan for
我也在Kaplan工作的东西
jetbrains so if you excuse me my coding
如果您对不起我的编码
examples will be in cotton but I
例子是棉花，但我
hopefully they'll be easier to incent
希望他们会更容易激励
for everybody and I'm really clueless
对于每个人，我真的很笨
about you guys so who is first of all
关于你们，谁首先
who has obviously if you came here
谁有明显的机会，如果你来这里
probably being writing some concurrent
可能正在写一些并发
code please raise your hands if you did
代码，请举手
okay okay so I see so so the most of you
好吧好吧，所以我看到了，所以你们大多数人
didn't so in a year you come to see
一年不是这样，你来看看
what's going on so I'll help you today
发生了什么事，所以我今天会帮助您
so today we're going to talk about share
所以今天我们要谈分享
it mutable state and that's kind of
它是易变的状态，
three words that really dread people
三个让人们真正恐惧的词
really know what it's about because when
真的知道这是因为什么时候
people who programmed for for for many
为许多人编程的人
years when they hear the word share it
他们听到这个词的岁月
will stay they they get different
会留下来，他们变得与众不同
associations maybe something like this
协会也许是这样的
you know when it all crashes and blue
你知道什么时候所有的崩溃和蓝色
screens or maybe it sounds like this you
屏幕，或者听起来像你
know that's kind of you know association
知道那种你知道交往
with people here because share instead
与这里的人，因为分享
was three things you you should never
三件事你永远都不要
ever put together you know you can have
曾经在一起，你知道你可以拥有
mutability you but separately you know
可变性，但您分别知道
sharing separately but when you do it
单独共享，但在您共享时
all together
全部一起
it's it's it's it's become a really hard
是的，这变得非常困难
so if it's that bad then why people is
所以如果那是那么糟糕，那么为什么人们
doing this so why we have this shared
这样做是为什么我们要共享
middle state and why Java supports it
中间状态以及Java为什么支持它
when many other modern languages do
当许多其他现代语言
support it why not why don't we go like
支持它，为什么不为什么我们不喜欢
and forbid it like there are some
并禁止它像有一些
languages that do completely forbid
完全禁止的语言
you're from Harry
你来自哈里
Oh state and there was this actually
哦，状态，实际上有这个
really simple like if you look at the
真的很简单，就像你看着
morning world and you have this you know
早晨的世界，你知道这个
word week data so I put a big
废话周数据，所以我把
big data and you have to do something
大数据，你必须做点什么
with it you know many times the your
有了它，你知道很多次
problem that you're trying to solve is
您要解决的问题是
you can't represent it with this pattern
你不能用这种模式代表它
you have this big data you split it in
您拥有这些大数据，您可以将其拆分
two batches then you do some processing
两批然后您做一些处理
with camapign the data then you collect
带有战利品的数据，然后您收集
the results in getting answer that's
得到答案的结果是
most of the problems I like that and the
我喜欢的大多数问题和
problems I like that are called
我喜欢的问题被称为
embarrassingly parallel that's actually
令人尴尬的是，实际上
the actual technical term the problems
实际技术术语存在的问题
in calling embarrass in parallel and
在同时叫尴尬和
because to solve them I mean the easy to
因为要解决它们，我的意思是容易
realize and you don't have to to go in
意识到，你不必走进
this scary world of shared mutable state
共享可变状态的可怕世界
because you know there's nothing shared
因为你知道没有共享
here you can scale it upskill diode into
在这里您可以将它放大二极管
cluster you can write your regular DNA
您可以编写常规DNA的簇
processing code let's framework that's
处理代码让我们建立一个框架
it's the bottom take care about
这是底部照顾
arranging only operation that's it if
仅安排操作，如果
the if your problem is like that you're
如果你的问题是那样的
a happy guy you you don't have to be
一个快乐的人，你不必
here however sometimes you have this big
在这里但是有时候你有这么大
big data but it is also like real-time
大数据，但它也像实时
or semi real-time oh it changes all the
或半实时哦，它会改变所有
time like for example stock quotations
时间，例如股票报价
change all the time you know your
一直改变你知道的时间
inventory in a big company something
大公司的存货
that you know status of users in social
您知道用户在社交网络中的状态
network like there's a lots of data it's
网络就像有很多数据一样
constantly changes and you have lots of
不断变化，你有很多
simultaneous requests coming to do
同时进行的请求
something with this data
与此数据有关的东西
you know compute it your portfolio you
你知道计算你的投资组合吗
know yet
还不知道
real-time statuses for users in your
您的用户的实时状态
social network do something like that
社交网络做类似的事情
and when you start trying to solve this
当您开始尝试解决这个问题时
problem in a both scalable and
可扩展性和
performant way there's simply no way to
高效的方式根本没有办法
to solve it which is in most performant
解决最有效的问题
and scalable without actually sharing
无需实际共享即可扩展
this big data which changes which is
改变的大数据是
minimal between all the current
在所有当前之间最小
concurrent processes then you have
并发进程，那么你有
I mean if you take the other approach
我的意思是如果您采取其他方法
you just okay let's not share anything
你就好吧，我们不要分享任何东西
you know then it gets a massive
你知道然后它变得巨大
duplication later
以后复制
I mean SEO and if data changes in real
我的意思是SEO，如果数据真实变化
time you have to deliver it in all the
时间，你必须在所有
copies etc a huge waste of resources so
复制等资源的巨大浪费，所以
many problems of this kind can be only
这类问题可能仅仅是
salt if you actually take this beta data
如果您实际使用此Beta数据，则添加盐
put it in some memory and access it
放入一些内存并访问它
concurrently for all the requests that
同时处理所有的请求
you have and this is of course duties
你有，这当然是职责
stuff like this is a really dark side
像这样的东西真的很阴暗
but I mean we have to embrace this dark
但我的意思是我们必须拥抱这个黑暗
side when we when we work with it I mean
一边当我们与我们合作时
there's simply no other way so let's
根本没有其他方法，所以让我们
let's come forward to this dark side and
让我们来到这黑暗的一面，
work with it in order for this
为此使用它
particular presentation we have to I
我们必须向我做的特别介绍
have to
不得不
it will straight you with some examples
它会带给你一些例子
so we'll have to pick some toy problem
所以我们必须选择一些玩具问题
and that's the hardest part
这是最难的部分
I mean peeking into a problem to
我的意思是偷看一个问题
showcase concurrency because to a
展示并发是因为
program never never real problem and
程序从来没有真正的问题，
will never show you the two problems
永远不会告诉你两个问题
that you'll encounter real life but for
你会遇到现实生活，但对于
those this particular problem I've built
那些我已经建立的特殊问题
a stack there isn't simple most people
一大堆人并不简单
no know how stacks work and you know it
不知道堆栈如何工作，你知道吗
will let us showcase some core concepts
让我们展示一些核心概念
they will be working with for sake is
他们将与之合作是
simple will get the Lincoln stack so
简单会得到林肯堆栈，所以
we'll have a node in a stack that has a
我们将在一个具有一个
next reference and the value of some
下一个参考和一些价值
type T and I'm doing my as I said my
输入T，然后按我说的做
examples in Kotlin just because a cotton
Kotlin的例子仅仅是因为棉花
is you know special English were
你知道特殊的英语吗
invented so or code fits on slide you
因此发明或代码适合您
know and because if I do it in Java you
知道，因为如果我用Java做，你
know it's a full side of code and you
知道这是代码的全部内容，而您
know in the Wisconsin III can fit
知道威斯康星州三世可以容纳
something else in addition to that and
除此之外，还有
that's what I need so oh I won't be
这就是我所需要的，所以我不会
scared it was Java anymore
担心它不再是Java
so the sec is simple so how it works
所以秒很简单，它是如何工作的
anyone starts with an empty stack that's
任何人都以一个空栈开始
some top variable with their null
一些具有null的顶级变量
pointer then we add an element to it and
指针，然后我们向其中添加一个元素，
it stopped once to attend its next is
它停下来一次参加下一个是
now then we can add another one element
现在，我们可以添加另一个元素
to
至
then switch top tweet and that's a stack
然后切换顶部推文，这是一个堆栈
contains two elements in me so that's
我内含两个元素，所以
that's that's real easy so push elements
那真的很容易，所以推元素
the stack is easy and we can easily
堆栈很容易，我们可以轻松地
write this code I mean we can just
写这段代码我是说我们可以
declare class for a stack we can declare
为堆栈声明类，我们可以声明
top variable and I'll push is just one
顶部变量，我将推只是一个
liner easy not not a video so that's our
班轮容易不是视频，这就是我们的
top that's a push so how do we pop an
顶部是一个推动，所以我们如何弹出
item from the circuit
电路中的项目
so we examine what the what the current
所以我们检查一下当前
element is the top and then we flip the
元素是顶部，然后我们翻转
top to the next one and we read the
回到下一个，我们阅读了
result and get an easy and just how it
结果并获得一个简单的方法
looks
看起来
that's the way it works so this which is
这就是它的工作方式，这就是
especially you know concise and coupling
特别是您知道简洁和结合
because you know I can I can fold my no
因为你知道我可以折叠我的不
checks into this nice syntactical cancer
检查这个漂亮的句法癌症
so it's really really like everything
所以真的很喜欢
fits on one slide that's very simple
可以放在一张非常简单的幻灯片上
second plantation so does it work of
第二种植园也是如此
course it works if I do it serially like
当然，如果我按顺序执行它会起作用
if I if only once threaded time works
如果我只有一次线程化时间有效
with my stat if I don't share it right
与我的统计信息，如果我不同意的话
everything works perfect but I said
一切正常，但我说
working if I actually share alright if
如果我真的同意，就可以工作
it's shared middle state if the stack is
如果堆栈是共享的中间状态
a partnership maybe I'm doing maybe I'm
伙伴关系也许我正在做也许我正在
doing kind of for example a pool of four
做例如四人池
big objects or for my data and pulling
大物件或用于我的数据和拉动
objects is easy to do with stack stack
堆栈很容易实现对象
stack is nice
堆栈很好
absolutely nice data structure to do a
绝对不错的数据结构
pool of objects so suppose I have a pool
对象池，假设我有一个池
of some buffers or a seller put in stack
一些缓冲区或卖方放在堆栈中
and now I have this big parallel
现在我有这么大的平行
processing and my many threads needs to
处理，我的许多线程需要
take items from the pool and put back
从游泳池拿东西，放回去
items into the pool so so what happens
物品放到游泳池里怎么办
if two threads try to push into stack
如果两个线程尝试推入堆栈
right so one of them comes you know
对，所以其中之一来了，你知道
weeds the top tries to add value B then
杂草顶端尝试增加值B，然后
the other comes with it up tries to add
另一个随之而来尝试添加
element C but now only one of them will
元素C，但现在只有其中一个会
succeed in updating the top and the
成功更新顶部和
other one will rewrite the top from the
另一个将重写
first one so we'll get in the end will
第一个，所以我们最终会得到
get only
只得到
two threats concurrently push will get
同时推动两个威胁
only one of them added to the stack and
其中只有一个添加到堆栈中，
this is a common problem this it's I
这是一个普遍的问题，是我
think you called it conflict and it's
认为你称它为冲突，这是
easy to solve in both Java ya Kotlin you
容易在Java Ya Kotlin中解决
just market synchronizing job it's a
只是市场同步工作，这是一个
keyword you know in in the cotton it's a
您在棉花中知道的关键字是
annotation but the concept is the same
注解，但概念相同
by marking it synchronize you you
通过标记它同步您
ensured mutual exclusion between
确保彼此之间的互斥
different threads that are trying to
试图不同的线程
push and pop and this way it prevents
推和弹出，这样可以防止
the problems that we saw but the
我们看到的问题，但
question we came here to understand it
我们来这里了解这个问题
does it scale okay so I saw the problem
它可以缩放吗，所以我看到了问题
now works but does it skill in order to
现在可以工作，但是可以熟练操作
figure out if it scales we have to
弄清楚它是否可以扩展，我们必须
understand what's called bilities and
了解所谓的能力和
some who measure it remember we'll just
一些测量它的人记得我们会
run a benchmark and we'll use this this
运行基准，我们将使用此
nice gem a framework that's I would
不错的一个框架，我会
recommend anyone who is writing
推荐任何正在写作的人
benchmark is open source on open source
基准测试是开源的
and I will have all the links at the end
我将在所有链接的末尾
it's open source on D on the Java side
它在Java方面是D上的开源
so and it's part of what man GDK so I
所以这是男人GDK的一部分，所以我
can just declare my benchmark which I
可以宣布我的基准
have a share stick and I will have
有一个共享棒，我将有
multiple threads just trying to push
多个线程只是试图推动
item set popping making sure they pop
弹出项目集以确保它们弹出
and one so the work my workload is real
因此我的工作量是真实的
simple just the sequence push pop I make
简单，只是我制作的序列推送弹出
sure that issue is pushes and pops OH
确保问题出在推挤过程中
stacks doesn't grow indefinitely it's
堆栈不会无限增长，而是
just limited in size and to measure how
只是大小有限并且要衡量
it scales
它缩放
I want this benchmark by wiring the
我希望通过连接
number of threats enter on it and in
威胁数量不断增加
order to make it realistic I've went and
为了使它变得现实，我去了
rented this the largest Amazon instance
租了这个最大的亚马逊实例
I could get my hands on with some extra
我可以多花些钱
large compute instance with you know
您知道的大型计算实例
Xeon processors 32 Hardware threads so
至强处理器32个硬件线程
like I think that's how you run your
就像我认为这就是您运行自己的方式
wheel application right you'll if you
车轮应用程序，如果您愿意
have lots of data you have this big
有很多数据，你有这么大
machine lots of memory and lots of
机器大量的内存和大量的
Hardware threads you'll load your data
您将加载数据的硬件线程
inside
内
machine and you will start all your data
机器，您将开始所有数据
processing threats will start working
处理威胁将开始起作用
with this data concurrently so the in
与此数据同时存在
this whole model that's basically this
整个模型基本上就是这个
wheel tour examples on model of that
那个模型的轮巡实例
kind of real-life processing if so I'm
一种现实生活中的处理方式
running this of real-life looking
运行这种真实的外观
machine and that's what I get what I get
机器，这就是我得到的
is that it's it does like 20 millions of
是因为它确实像两千万
these operations per second in one
这些操作每秒合二为一
thread but then if I add more threads it
线程，但是如果我添加更多线程，
doesn't become better it's actually
并没有变好，实际上
become worse you know it's especially
变得更糟，你知道这尤其
working two threads which kinds of
工作两个线程哪种
interesting effect when we have two
当我们有两个时，有趣的效果
threads is like the worst of the worst
线程就像最坏的情况一样
but as which number of threads kind of
但是作为哪种线程数
stabilizes and but still it does not
稳定，但仍然没有
perform as well as if it were running
表现和运行一样
just a single thread so differently this
只是一个线程，所以与此不同
kind of problem in the solution to it is
解决方案中的一种问题是
we're adding more threads doesn't make
我们添加更多线程不会
it doesn't make it better it doesn't let
它不会使它变得更好，它不会让
it push more operations per second so
它每秒推送更多操作，因此
it's what's called doesn't skill why
这就是所谓的不懂为什么
doesn't kill because because I think
不会杀死，因为我想
that its technical contention so because
那是因为它的技术争议
when one threads perform said for
当一个线程执行说
example a pop and the other thread in
例如流行音乐和其他线程
the middle of the pop comes and tries to
流行音乐的中间来了，并试图
do it it can't do it has to wait because
做它不能做它必须等待，因为
synchronized is a mutual exclusion
同步是互斥的
concept you know we'll have to wait
你知道我们必须等待的概念
until the first pop completes and only
直到第一个流行音乐完成并且只有
then we can pop an item from the stack
然后我们可以从堆栈中弹出一个项目
so that's that's one one problem with
所以那是一个问题
synchronization which all usual solution
同步所有通常的解决方案
to the concurrency is that under
并发的是
contention we're starting to wait we
争执，我们开始等待我们
cannot do things concurrently like
不能同时做某事
really seen synchronized keywords and
确实看到过同步关键字和
locks they limit our concurrency because
锁定它们限制了我们的并发性，因为
we have to since have to be done
我们必须这样做
serially more more so it adds overhead
串行更多，因此增加了开销
because every time I stumble into the
因为每次我偶然发现
log by other thread I have to contact
我必须联系其他线程记录
tsuge that's why it falls down under
tsu，这就是为什么它跌倒
when we have multiple say it's not just
当我们有多个说法不只是
stays flat like we can only push more
保持平稳，就像我们只能推动更多
operations per second we actually under
实际每秒操作数
contention when we have lots of doing it
当我们有很多事情要做的时候
we're pushing less operations per second
我们正在减少每秒的操作
because there's X overhead involved in
因为涉及X的开销
managing
管理
but that just one problem with locks the
但这只是锁的一个问题
other problem is ox is dead locks when
另一个问题是，当黄牛死锁时
we start to writing a rake in our
我们开始写我们的耙子
application we synchronize with locks as
我们与锁同步的应用程序
we add more and more locks in our amps
我们在放大器中添加了越来越多的锁
we add the contents risk intron and
我们添加内容风险内含子，
daggered locks in the situation where
匕首锁在什么情况下
you know I cannot take a lot because
你知道我不能接受很多，因为
it's taking but some other thread who
这需要但是其他一些线程
turns out to be waiting for for the log
原来是在等待日志
that I keep and that's that that's
我保留的就是那
that's the other scalability problem
这是另一个可扩展性问题
with locks were scalability not in terms
带锁的不是可扩展性
of how many Hardware course I have but
我有多少硬件课程，但是
skull built in terms of how large my
我的头骨有多大
project is the logic my project becomes
项目是我的项目成为的逻辑
the harder it becomes to maintain if I'm
如果我变得更难维持
using locks in it so that's why we're
在其中使用锁，这就是为什么我们
for either of those problems were
因为这些问题之一
turning our sighting to lock for
将目光锁定
algorithms algorithms that don't use
不使用的算法
locks to solve this same problem and the
锁来解决同样的问题，
to understand how lock for algorithms
了解如何锁定算法
work how they don't don't run into the
工作如何不碰到
problems with concurrency but without
并发问题，但没有
using locks let's consider what prevents
使用锁，让我们考虑一下防止
us from pushing two items concurrently
我们不能同时推动两个项目
into the stacks the problem is that when
进入堆栈的问题是
we've prepared to push an item we expect
我们已经准备好推出我们期望的产品
that the top is still pointing to the
顶部仍然指向
old item and we want to update it to the
旧项目，我们想将其更新为
new item wearing short leave this deck
穿着短的新物品离开这个甲板
if only we can do this operation
如果可以的话
atomically making sure nobody else can
从原子上确保其他人不能
interfere and add their element faster
干扰并更快地添加其元素
than we did and that's exactly this
比我们做的就是这
atomic update from expected reference to
从预期参考到的原子更新
the new one is is called
新的叫做
is there is there's an A for search
有没有要搜索的A
operation the name is compared and set
操作名称进行比较和设置
and there is a class in Java called
Java中有一个叫做
atomic reference that provides us such
提供给我们这样的原子参考
functionality it's a it's a class
功能是一类
actually you know it's it's a part of
实际上你知道这是它的一部分
GDK so we can use it from any given
GDK，因此我们可以从任何给定中使用它
language on this example we'll be in the
在此示例中，我们将使用
following slides using it from code line
从代码行开始使用幻灯片
because it just a class we can use and
因为这只是我们可以使用的类
inside it contains two volatile variable
它里面包含两个volatile变量
you can get it or you can compare and
你可以得到它，或者你可以比较和
set it you can prime said is that's
设置它，您可以说是
atomic update I'm updating variable
我正在更新变量的原子更新
under condition that nobody else has has
在没有其他人拥有的情况下
changes is still equal to the expected
变化仍然等于预期
value it's available since ages since
重视自从
1.5 and I mean it's real prison a long
1.5，我的意思是，这是很长时间的真实监狱
time ago 1.5 and job was the first
之前1.5，工作是第一
language major language who kind of
语言专业语言是谁的
standardized such operations compare
标准化操作比较
said like in c plus plus he used to be
就像在c plus中说的那样，他曾经是
forced to use like vendor specific
被迫像特定于供应商一样使用
extensions some libraries it wasn't part
扩展了部分库
of the language in became partners
语言中的成为伙伴
language in c++ only recently and that's
C ++语言只是最近才有的
why when you start reading literature
为什么当你开始阅读文学
and concurrent computing on logarithms
和对数并发计算
you often find examples in java because
您经常在Java中找到示例，因为
because java has me has standardized
因为Java让我标准化了
this kind of code way longer than than
这种代码比
any other language so i mean that's easy
任何其他语言，所以我的意思是很容易
so we have yeah we'll have well you may
所以我们有，你可以
compare and said that's always how we
比较并说，这始终是我们的方式
use it we use it by replacing our top
使用它，我们通过替换顶部使用它
variable instead of being a variable
变量而不是变量
that we're going to change is going to
我们将要改变的是
be value we're not going to reach the
是有价值的，我们不会达到
top itself instead it's going to contain
顶部本身，它将包含
atomic reference and we'll be using this
原子引用，我们将使用它
atomic reference it's one change itself
原子引用本身就是一种改变
but we'll be updating it and the way you
但是我们会更新它以及您的方式
write lock for algorithms is by
算法的写锁由
following this pattern so we read the
按照这种模式，所以我们阅读
current value and we're using yet we
当前值，我们正在使用，但我们
decide how we want updated in this case
决定在这种情况下我们如何更新
we want to create a new node with
我们要创建一个新节点
pointing to the well you were just read
指向你刚刚读的井
with our value and we'll try to perform
用我们的价值，我们将尽力执行
this atomic update through comparing set
通过比较集的原子更新
and if it's successful we return if it's
如果成功，我们会返回
not successful just loop which is slow
不成功，只是循环慢
passing or successful we just retry
通过或成功，我们只是重试
until we successfully push it and this
直到我们成功推动它
pattern is you'll find in almost every
模式几乎可以在每个
lock tree algorithm it's really powerful
锁树算法真的很强大
pattern because it lets us solve the
模式，因为它可以让我们解决
problem
问题
concurrently modified data structure
同时修改的数据结构
without using any law whatsoever I said
我没有说任何法律
that's the the real power of walk free
那才是真正的自由行走的力量
you know and but the pattern is simple
你知道，但是模式很简单
we can similar right pop I mean it's
我们可以类似的流行音乐，我的意思是
it's I won't go step by step here but
我不会在这里一步一步走，但是
it's the same idea we with the current
这与我们当前的想法相同
value we try to updated necks of
值，我们尝试更新
successful return well if not you try
成功的回报很好，如果你不尝试
but notice that here to write this we're
但请注意，在这里写下这个
using atomic reference class and I mean
使用原子引用类，我的意思是
let's remember why we started doing
让我们记住为什么我们开始做
lock-free so our end goal in this
无锁，因此我们的最终目标
presentation is to make a scalable
演示是为了使可伸缩性
application and then scale with somewhat
应用程序，然后稍微扩展
implies it's going to be fast but by
暗示它会很快，但是
using atomic reference we can create
使用原子引用，我们可以创建
another layer in direction instead of
方向的另一层而不是
just working with the top variable
只是使用顶部变量
directly we've created yet another
我们直接创建了另一个
object atomic reference and we're
对象原子引用，我们
constantly indirectly going there by
不断地间接去那里
reference into another object which
引用到另一个对象
might be a key for this small example
可能是这个小例子的关键
but in larger application we'll have a
但在更大的应用程序中，我们将有一个
lots of concurrent options it might be
许多并发选项可能是
might be a performance problem so so
可能是性能问题，所以
it's a trap here that then we need we
这是一个陷阱，那么我们需要我们
need to solve it somehow there are two
需要以某种方式解决它有两个
solutions first of all what we would
解决方案首先我们会
like to do is we would like to be able
我们要做的就是
to directly modify node if there's
直接修改节点（如果有）
actual volatile might've modifier in
实际的挥发物可能已经在
Java or volatile tation cotton that you
您的Java或挥发性棉
can use to specify that I'm going to
可以用来指定我要
modify variable from multiple threads
从多个线程修改变量
and it's is going to ensure all the
这将确保所有
query memory semantics for you but how I
为您查询内存语义，但我如何
actually do compare and set I can read
实际上比较并设置我可以阅读
and write it but how do I comprehend
并写出来，但我怎么理解
operations that they need for this
他们为此需要的操作
atomic update one solution is a class
原子更新一个解决方案是一类
called atomic reference updater which
称为原子引用更新器
also defines this Java in five and john
也用五和约翰定义了这个Java
1.5 and it's it's pretty ugly class in
1.5，这是一个非常丑陋的课程
the sense that you know it's even its
你知道它甚至是它的感觉
signatures look scary and when you use
签名看起来很吓人，使用时
it you have to earn a living example in
你必须在
Java because there's no ugly code and
Java，因为没有丑陋的代码，
that's why they're in
这就是为什么他们在
Java so you'll have to defy
Java，因此您必须反抗
multi-variable
多变量
and you'll have to define static-filled
而且您必须定义静态填充
and that's using this new update or get
这就是使用此新更新或获取
your first job data which is pretty big
您的第一份工作数据很大
amount of boilerplate doesn't even fit
样板甚至不适合
on my slide horizontally and then in the
在我的幻灯片上水平然后在
code when you scamper and said instead
代码，当您匆忙说相反
of writing it naturally like I want to
像我想要的那样自然地编写它
update top I'm writing very in natural
更新顶部我写得很自然
style I have using this constant to call
我有使用此常量调用的样式
compare and say degree so it it just
比较并说出程度，就这样
doesn't look like it looks like
看起来不像
boilerplate not a real code but it works
样板不是真正的代码，但可以工作
it lets me avoid this extra extra field
它让我避免了这个额外的额外领域
and the other solution has appeared just
而另一个解决方案已经出现
recently it's built in Java 9 in Joanna
最近在Joanna中以Java 9内置
has the thing called war handle it's a
有一个叫做战争手柄的东西
new new abstraction Joe and I it's it's
新的新抽象乔，我是
somewhat similar to atomic reference
有点类似于原子参考
update in the sense that you also can
您也可以更新
compare set through it and use it very
比较设置并非常使用它
similar way just the code even more
类似的方式只是代码
argue later you have to write even more
争论以后，你必须写更多
boilerplate to use it so I mean
使用它的样板，所以我的意思是
unfortunately that's kind of progress in
不幸的是，这是
this respect but it you have tried
这种尊重，但你已经尝试过
mobile play to initialize it looks
移动播放以初始化它的外观
similar more boilerplate but then you
类似更多样板，但然后你
use it again in the same ugly way it
以同样的丑陋方式再次使用它
just doesn't look natural since I write
自从我写以来看起来并不自然
lots of lock-free code in this
许多无锁代码
concurrent code and part of my day job
并发代码和我日常工作的一部分
and I can't say when I start coding and
我不能说何时开始编码
calling you you start you start to
打电话给你，你开始，你开始
notice all this boilerplate you know
注意所有您知道的样板
because you're so much less boilerplate
因为你少了很多样板
in coding code so you kind of try to
在编码中，所以您尝试
issue it as much as possible so I wrote
尽可能地发行它，所以我写了
this very simple library called atomic
这个非常简单的库称为atom
phone so instead of going through this
电话，而不是通过这个
boilerplate I can just write
我可以写的样板
top as if it was an atomic reference I
好像它是原子引用一样
just have a nice function called atomic
只是有一个叫做原子的好函数
that that trusts me like it's real
相信我的感觉是真实的
compact way to declare the fact that top
声明顶部事实的紧凑方法
should be atomic variable that contains
应该是包含的原子变量
note maybe now and it's initially now
请注意，现在可能是现在
the inner just use it just like I did
内部就像我一样使用它
with atomic reference so I you stop
与原子参考，所以我停下来
comparing set and that's it this but the
比较集，仅此而已
trick is that I code it like atomic
诀窍是我像原子一样编码
reference and I compile it into Java
参考，并将其编译为Java
byte code just like Road but then there
字节码就像道一样，但是在那里
a bytecode pass processor who actually
一个字节码传递处理器，实际上
chose this code into coded using atomic
选择此代码以使用原子编码
reference filled up later so behind it
参考资料已填满，因此在其后面
since it's so I don't have to write this
因为是这样，我不必写这个
boilerplate and I let the to write this
样板，我让写这个
boilerplate for me and that's that's
对我来说就是样板
that's kind of what what kind of the
那是什么样的
progress in you know computer
你知道计算机的进步
programming what's about your as you
像你一样编程
know you go into a high level of
知道你进入高水平
assertion you let tools do boilerplate
断言你让工具做样板
for you they don't write yourself the
为你，他们不写你自己
good thing about it that without
好东西，没有
changing my source I can turn flip and
改变我的来源，我可以翻转和
switch and have it emit the code that
切换并发出代码
using more handle so I don't have to
使用更多的手柄，所以我不必
change a single line of my code for that
为此更改一行代码
of course the question is is was it
当然，问题是
worth it
值得
okay so we did all the step will learn
好的，所以我们做的所有步骤都会学到
how to write lock free stack even would
怎么写无锁堆栈
even learn how to write it so it's nice
甚至学习如何写，所以很好
you know and can work around different
你知道并且可以解决不同的问题
api's but addy like why what what did we
api的但阿迪喜欢为什么我们做了什么
win anything so let's measure it and
赢什么，让我们衡量一下，
when we measure it you know the results
当我们测量它时，您知道结果
want look they kind of mixed so for
想要看起来他们有点混杂，所以
single thread case there's a definitely
单线程的情况下肯定有
win and that's one advantage of our
赢了，这是我们的优势之一
algorithms that they just have more more
他们拥有更多的算法
they're more performant when there is no
没有的时候他们会表现得更好
contention a single thread case but
争用单线程情况，但
unfortunately it's kind of in contention
不幸的是，这有点争执
case we're losing a lot as you became
情况下，随着您
we're working if not working much worse
我们正在努力，如果不做得更糟
than it worked with logs so why why is
比它与日志工作的原因，为什么呢？
that wildly one third case faster is
快三分之一的情况是
obvious because we don't have locks it's
很明显，因为我们没有锁
just much less overhead but why we're
开销要少得多，但为什么我们要
having such worse results like several
结果像几个
times less operations per second in the
每秒减少的操作次数
ministry s case the reason is it that
事工的原因是
water algorithms also suffer from
水算法也遭受
contention but they suffer in a
竞争，但他们遭受
different way because when lock free to
不同的方式，因为当锁自由
log preparations overlap the second one
日志准备与第二个准备工作重叠
not just wait until the first one
不只是等到第一个
completes it wastes the whole work it
完成它浪费了整个工作
tries to do it because it tries to
尝试这样做，因为它试图
update but then encounters that the
更新，但随后遇到
other thread want the race and did it
其他线程想要比赛并且做到了
did it before so it has to try the whole
之前做过，所以必须尝试整个
operation so the
操作，所以
fact of contention on log preparation is
关于日志准备的争论事实是
much more pronounced and there of course
当然更明显
there are a lot of techniques to olivey
橄榄有很多技术
the problem there are lots of papers on
这个问题有很多论文
how to make a lot for algorithm
如何为算法赚钱
basically by doing tricks like you know
基本上是通过做一些你知道的技巧
exponential back-off a proper spinning
指数回退适当的旋转
ceteris better others worse combiners
ceteris更好的其他人更糟糕的组合器
lots of papers that apply these are that
许多适用这些的论文是
techniques in certain situation well you
在某些情况下的技巧
can actually get performance of
可以真正获得
logarithms on par with synchronous all
对数与全部同步
then while still keeping this good case
然后在保持这种情况下
of being passed in knock non container
在非集装箱敲门
case but we're not going to go into
情况下，但我们不打算讨论
there I mean because usually practice
我的意思是因为通常练习
you'll never need this advancing
你永远不需要这种前进
techniques and now I'll show you why
技术，现在我将向您展示为什么
first of all let's see whether we had
首先让我们看看我们是否有
our problem is to toy like we first of
我们的问题是先像我们一样玩
all we've looked at it to a problem to
我们所看到的所有问题
start with the stack is not something
从堆栈开始不是什么
you typically work with typically your
您通常会与您的
data structures are way more complex and
数据结构更复杂，
they're just a stack you have some maybe
他们只是一堆，你也许有一些
you know code database that's your
你知道代码数据库就是你的
update concurrently or something else
同时更新或其他
that that sits in updating it it takes
那就是更新它需要
much more time so let's try to simulate
更多的时间，让我们尝试模拟
it let's let's add let's take it more
让我们来添加让我们来更多
real but you know artificially inflating
真实，但您知道人为膨胀
the time of our current operation by
我们目前的运营时间
just spending some time and site we'll
只是花一些时间和地点，我们会
do this both for our algorithm wheels
为我们的算法轮做这两个
locks and the same change for a lock for
锁和锁的相同更改
implementation and let's see how they
实施，让我们看看他们如何
behave that's what we see because we've
表现那就是我们所看到的，因为我们已经
our operations became longer we don't we
我们的运营时间更长了我们不是
we don't see much difference in there
我们在那里看不出太大的区别
single thread performance anymore
单线程性能不再
because this over here of locks is now
因为这里的锁现在是
small compared to the cost of operation
与运营成本相比较小
itself but we still see that lock three
本身，但我们仍然看到那个锁三
algorithms don't shine here under
算法在这里不闪耀
contention the same rule kicks in you
争夺同样的规则
know under contention locks degree but
知道在竞争锁度下，但是
now they degrade like there's no this
现在它们像没有这个一样退化
strange d-pad to thread case but
奇怪的D垫到线程情况下，但
and they stay pretty constant degraded
他们保持不变的退化
with a pretty constant and lock-free
相当稳定且无锁
algorithm degrade under contention
算法在竞争下退化
because again the same problem they have
因为他们又遇到了同样的问题
to retry operation which is now became
重试现在已成为的操作
more complex but there's by the way less
更复杂，但顺便说一句
less difference in their performance
他们的表现差异较小
someone so I promise here that's or
有人，所以我保证在这里是
lock-free should be good so what's
无锁应该很好，那是什么
what's the reason
什么原因
let's try to lay a workload whether this
让我们尝试为这
workload really representative of what
工作量真的代表什么
we do with our data structures and of
我们处理我们的数据结构
course is not because usually when we
当然不是因为通常当我们
have this big data problem that's
有这样的大数据问题
updates in real time
实时更新
usually it's updates occasionally
通常它偶尔会更新
compared to the number of queries and
与查询数量相比
reads there - you're doing against it
在那儿读书-您正在反对
and that's that's really common pattern
那是很常见的模式
when you face this ability in big data
当您在大数据中面对这种能力时
problem because if the data is big you
问题是因为如果数据很大，您
know only small bits of pieces of it
只知道其中的一小部分
update so every piece of data updates
更新，以便每条数据都更新
relatively rare compared to the number
与数量相比相对稀有
of virus reports and read operations
病毒报告和读取操作
that have - that have to see what the
拥有-必须看到什么
current value is so we'll workloads are
当前值是，所以我们将工作量
mostly dominated so in order to simulate
主要是为了模拟
this will add we'll add in our operation
这将添加我们将添加我们的操作
will be twisted push and pop will do
将被扭曲推和流行会做
some weeds will peak at the top of the
一些杂草会在顶部
stack measure it's one there will do ten
堆栈测量是一个，将执行十
times
次
so in this going to ten to one basically
所以这基本上是十比一
ten Whisperer perturb dates actually in
实际上有十个耳语扰动日期
our workload in the peak operation for
我们在高峰运营中的工作量
synchronize implemented in this is easy
同步实现很容易
we just we just reach top well your war
我们只是达到您的战争而已
if it's null return now for lock free
如果为null，请立即返回以获取无锁
implementation that's also easy we do
实现起来也很容易
the same change and you know withers and
同样的变化，你知道枯萎，
implement peak for lock reads especially
实现锁读取的峰值，特别是
simple implantation so let's see what's
简单的植入，让我们看看是什么
going on now the picture is totally
现在，图片完全是
different
不同
first of all the throughput of the lock
首先锁的吞吐量
from finish now significantly
从现在开始到现在
outperforming the
表现优于
simply significantly second they now
他们现在仅次于
catch up under increasing number of
在越来越多的情况下赶上
threat threats and that's that's clear
威胁威胁，这很明显
demonstrates were locked free algorithms
演示被锁定的免费算法
chime Laufer algorithms shine in weed
编钟劳弗算法在杂草中闪耀
dominated workloads when you read your
阅读您的工作负载时
data much more often than you update
数据比您更新的频率要高得多
them because with lock-free weeds don't
他们，因为无锁杂草不会
never there's no loop there's no reason
永远没有循环，没有理由
Locker algorithm never suffer from
储物柜算法永远不会遭受
contention they could just weed the
他们可以除草
current value while weeds of the
杂草的当前值
synchronize data structure that's
同步的数据结构
protected by logs they have to suffer
受日志保护，他们必须受苦
they they have to wait until the writers
他们必须等到作家
change their modifications and it's not
改变他们的修改，不是
you see it's not that you know some
你看到的不是你知道一些
people think oh no problem I'll just
人们认为哦，没问题，我只是
remove synchronize from Maurice it's not
从莫里斯删除同步不是
that simple because ability to remove
这么简单，因为删除的能力
this sin question or it it possibly
这个罪恶问题或可能
depends what data structure it is the
取决于它是什么数据结构
basically depends on whether you can do
基本上取决于您是否可以做
it at least semi log free and again can
它至少半免费，然后可以再次
you shoot the logs for weeding for
您拍摄原木进行除草
example if you take the regular hash map
例如，如果您使用常规哈希图
that's in the GDK and you think oh you
在GDK中，您认为哦，您
know synchronizing on every hash max
知道每个哈希最大同步
getting expensive let's listen
越来越贵，让我们听听
translation on when I put into hash map
当我放入哈希图时的翻译
and leave all my hash map guess not
并留下我所有的哈希图不
surprise for pure formats because you
纯格式的惊喜，因为您
know because it's doesn't let me scale
知道，因为那不会让我缩放
and you'll find that it just doesn't
然后您会发现它并没有
work I mean I've seen instance in
工作，我是说我看过
production where people forget into
人们忘记的生产
synchronization read and you know hash
同步读取，您知道哈希
map just hand to some moment when you
将您的手映射到某个时刻
starting to read without
开始阅读而没有
synchronization you end up in some crazy
同步你最终会陷入疯狂
states where the read that is not
指出读取的不是
synchronize just just hand once into the
只同步一次
infinite loop so not every structure
无限循环，所以不是每个结构
unless the data is designed to allow
除非数据旨在允许
lock for weeds you can adjust say okay I
锁定杂草，你可以调整说好吧
don't need locks on reading it see but
不需要锁定就可以阅读，但是
let's see interest to see what happens
让我们看看有兴趣看看会发生什么
if it's even more read emanated if you
如果您阅读更多
have hundred reads you see as the
有一百次阅读，您认为
lockrey becomes even better like it's
洛克瑞变得更好，就像它
now clear clear outperforms
现在明显胜过明显
limitation but see I'll have this deep
限制，但请参阅我将深入了解
is still one thread the faster more
还是一个线程，速度越快
threats
威胁
you know slower but where's the
你知道慢一点，但是在哪里
scalability so the whole topic of the
可扩展性，所以整个主题
talk was Caleb and here I show you the
谈话是Caleb，在这里我向您展示
most as you add this slower everything
大多数情况下，您添加的速度会变慢
works so then what was the point of
起作用，那么什么是重点
having this huge 32 Hardware threads
具有如此庞大的32个硬件线程
machine to run this code if just any
计算机运行此代码（如果有）
more stress just makes everything floor
更大的压力只会使一切变得艰难
the reason is that again the workload we
原因是我们的工作量
have is artificial
有人造的
in reality you never have like all your
实际上，您永远不会喜欢所有的
threads badger in to the single day
badge到一天
distortion that never is a case well
永远不会出现这种情况的失真
know if you have a shared data that's
知道您是否有共享数据
shared mutable data in your code you
在代码中共享可变数据
usually with something from it then you
通常带有一些东西，那么你
do something with it you do some
用它做点事
computation processing it's not like you
计算处理不像你
read it read it read it constantly it's
读它读它不断读它是
never like that and you don't update it
从来没有那样，你不更新
console it's never like that you you
控制台永远不会像你一样
receive some data from Network parses
从网络解析接收一些数据
that update you moves you some requests
更新后，您会提出一些要求
read some data do some processing reply
读一些数据做一些处理回复
you know it's never Unicode never better
你知道它永远不会Unicode永远不会更好
sin to the single you know single day
罪恶你知道的单身一天
search all the time some work law that
一直在搜索一些工作规律
we'll be measuring so far it's
到目前为止，我们将进行测量
completely non representative of the
完全不代表
actual were close you'll encounter in
实际的亲密接触
practice in practice your clothes will
练习练习，你的衣服会
look something like this
看起来像这样
that's the best thing we can model the
这是我们可以建模的最好的方法
real-life workloads in this in as a
现实生活中的工作量
micro test so we'll just consume some
微测试，所以我们只消耗一些
CPU between you know every we'd to
您之间的CPU知道我们要做的每一件事
simulate the fact that in real
模拟真实的事实
application you're doing something
您正在执行的应用程序
instead of just reading and of course
不只是读书，当然
we'll do this for all our both you know
我们会尽力做到这一点
lock free and Link it implementation and
免费锁定并链接实现和
let's see what happens and that's that's
让我们看看会发生什么，那就是
where we clearly see the scale of this
我们可以清楚地看到这个规模
i've initially promised you because you
我最初答应你是因为你
see here that now actually both for link
看到这里，现在实际上都是链接
stack and for lock free as i increase
堆栈，随着我的增加而无锁
the number of
的数量
when I run my code I get more privations
当我运行代码时，我得到了更多的特权
per second because you know they can do
每秒，因为您知道他们可以做到
more of those processing concurrently
更多的同时处理
and you see that in those more will
你会看到更多的
worsen errors scalability of lock-free
错误加剧了无锁的可扩展性
clearly better than scalability of links
明显优于链接的可伸缩性
if they start now they start at some
如果他们现在开始，他们将从某个地方开始
point because compared to the cost of
点，因为相比于成本
the other CPU expense of the other
其他的其他CPU费用
operation it is the same their minor
操作是相同的，他们的未成年人
compared to the you know to the spin
与你知道的相比
that we've added but as number of firsts
我们添加的但作为第一的数量
increase we see the squabbles of La
增加，我们看到拉的争吵
falourdel's clearly clear bed and
法洛德尔的床很干净
actually yes
其实，是
how many Hardware threads our machine
我们的机器有多少个硬件线程
has because you see it's increases in
有，因为你看到它在增加
who's locked up until we have 32 threads
直到我们有32个线程为止
and says flats after that because I mean
然后说公寓，因为我的意思是
there's no reason to have any more
没有理由再有更多了
threats than like with the Machine I was
威胁比我以前的机器要好
running that on has just 32 threads so
运行它只有32个线程，所以
adding physical you know Hardware
添加物理您知道的硬件
threads so anymore
线程如此
you know threads because all our threats
你知道线程，因为我们所有的威胁
are consuming CPU they need anymore does
正在消耗他们需要的CPU
not do any good but the good thing is it
没有任何好处，但好处是
doesn't harm either on the real size
不会损害实际尺寸
number of threads we don't see any
看不到的线程数
decline when we over subscribe our
当我们过度订阅时下降
machine and that's very important for
机器，这对于
practical applications because you know
实际应用，因为您知道
in practice if you especially if you
在实践中，如果你特别是如果你
program with threads in deviant world
异常世界中带有线程的程序
you might for virus reasons might have
您可能出于病毒原因可能有
way more threats than you have CPU cores
比您拥有的CPU核心更多的威胁
for example of bein when working on
例如在工作时的贝因
versed in the rest applications have
精通其余应用程序
seen applications that run hundreds of
看到运行数百个应用程序
threads in much on machines that support
在支持的机器上大量线程化
only 64 Hardware threads and that's
只有64个硬件线程，那就是
normal because you might be might need
正常，因为您可能需要
those hundreds work with database or
那数百个人使用数据库或
with other blocking operations but the
与其他阻止操作，但
same time in my application I have some
同时在我的应用程序中，我有一些
shared data structures like the
共享的数据结构，例如
constantly update and I want to read
不断更新，我想阅读
them to do
他们要做
baris analytics like figuring out what's
baris分析，例如找出问题所在
the current stock prices and for those
当前的股价以及那些
you know I I wanted to scale
你知道我想扩大规模
want access to the shared data to slow
希望访问共享数据的速度变慢
down the rest of my work and I wanted as
剩下的工作我想
little as little barrier as possible and
尽可能少的障碍，并且
that's that's good that's you know it's
那是很好，那是你知道的
number I think you did it doesn't become
数字，我认为你做到了，并没有成为
worse so the the kind of a lesson here
更糟糕的是，这里的教训
is that we need when we measure
是我们测量时需要的
performance we need to make sure we ask
我们需要确保性能
the ask the right question is the most
问正确的问题是最
challenge actually task into measuring
挑战实际任务进行衡量
performance especially concurrent code
性能，尤其是并发代码
and especially if you're trying to
特别是如果您要
assess such fleeting characteristics
评估这种短暂的特征
like scalability is us there are
就像可扩展性一样
questions and like modeling your
问题，喜欢建模
workload is is really exercise it pays
工作量真的是锻炼，它值得
off so if you are into into the task of
因此，如果您沉迷于
making sure you got scales
确保你有秤
I mean don't never you know don't think
我的意思是永远不要你不知道
like you can just you know um eat this
就像你可以知道你吃这个
exercise of trying to model your
尝试为您的模型建模
workflow I mean modeling workflow is
我的工作流程是对工作流程进行建模
important because if you don't model
很重要，因为如果您不建模
your flow correctly you are not getting
您的流程正确，您没有得到
the right answers out of your
正确答案
measurements and then when you have a
测量，然后当你有一个
great model for a workflow you know you
您认识的工作流程的绝佳模型
can then you can compare what's
那你可以比较一下
implementations and see that if you have
实现，看看是否有
a reader manator workload and the real
阅读器管理员的工作量和实际
life condition lock-free
生活条件无锁
algorithms often outperform the
算法通常胜过
velvetiness who has logs and if you want
谁有原木，如果想要的话
to learn more about that this is true
进一步了解这是真的
great book I would recommend the one is
我会推荐的一本好书是
Java concurrency and practice by Brian
Brian的Java并发和实践
it's really good book for practitioners
对从业者来说真的是一本好书
with the only downside that it has
它唯一的缺点
examples in Java this is slightly too
Java中的示例，这也有点
verbose but I mean there's they easily
冗长，但我的意思是容易
translate it in Catalan II and you know
翻译成加泰罗尼亚语II，你知道
save you a lot of typing but and the
为您节省了很多打字时间，但是
other book is more from the theoretical
另一本书更多是从理论上讲的
standpoint they are the most processor
立场，他们是最处理器
programming by hello here's a bit and it
你好编程这里有一点，它
goes deeper into the theory of
深入研究
concurrency
并发
explains lots of interesting in
解释了很多有趣的
non-trivial
不平凡的
lock-free algorithms in a deep way
深入了解无锁算法
so for anyone who is interested or -
因此，对于任何有兴趣的人或-
that's two bucks in a third-order you
三阶是两块钱
can start with either one depending how
可以从任何一个开始，具体取决于
your mind works like you're more
你的想法像你一样
theoretically or practically inclined
理论上或实践上倾向于
there - good complement each other
在那里-很好的互补
really well and really nice read and
非常好，非常好阅读，
some links at the end so I mean I hope
最后一些链接，所以我希望
the slides will be posted so the gym age
幻灯片将被张贴，以适应健身年龄
that I've used for benchmarking the the
我用来基准测试
reference to content that I use my
引用我使用的内容
examples and atomic food that lets me
例子和原子食物让我
write it all in a nice you know concise
简明扼要地写下来
way and I'm open to questions
方式，我很开放
yeah the bench managed image you run it
是的，您可以在工作台管理的图像上运行它
with the number of threats you want and
以及您想要的威胁数量
it will just runs as as many threats as
它将与威胁一样多
you ask it for you know because my state
你问它是因为我的状态
is called per benchmark there is a scope
被称为每个基准有一个范围
benchmark annotation so it will share
基准注释，因此它将共享
this state between all the stress and it
所有压力和它之间的这种状态
just they do well use operations per
只是他们很好地使用了操作
second so in vacations of my this is
第二，在我的假期中，这是
this is my benchmark method and the
这是我的基准测试方法，
metric I show is up operations operation
我显示的指标是向上操作
is one invocation of this this function
是对此功能的一次调用
number of methods successfully completed
成功完成的方法数量
medicals per second that's that's a
每秒的医疗数据就是
measurement that's just default in Gmail
在Gmail中只是默认值
you can configure what you want to see
您可以配置要查看的内容
you can see like how many nine seconds
你可以看到大概九秒钟
or microseconds into but default is
或微秒，但默认值为
operations per second
每秒操作
yeah there are lots of no of course
是的，当然有很多没有
there are lots of ways I mean actually
我实际上有很多方法
if you read this book there's a whole
如果你读这本书，那么整个
chapter on virus techniques to make it
关于病毒技术的章节
better there's a whole chapter I mean I
最好有一整章，我是说我
just just this prison is too small to go
只是这个监狱太小了而已
my goal was to if you get interested if
我的目标是如果你感兴趣的话
and if you want to know how to do just
如果你想知道怎么做
read this book excuse me yeah yep there
看过这本书，对不起，是的
is a lot of libraries first of all Java
Java首先是很多库
library contains some of the lock for
库包含一些用于
algorithms in the standard library like
标准库中的算法，例如
concurrent hash phase map and and and
并发哈希阶段图和
others concurrent skip list so but the
其他并发跳过列表，所以
the well I found from a practical
我从实践中发现的井
experience and if you face a real life
经验，如果你面对现实生活
problem the problem is locked algorithms
问题问题是锁定算法
they don't compose so somebody gave me
他们不写作，所以有人给了我
you know ready to use concurrent hash
你知道准备使用并发哈希
map and I have a slightly different
地图和我有一点不同
problem like some operations it doesn't
像某些操作一样的问题
natively support I cannot unlike I
天生的支持，我不能不像我
cannot just extend it there's no way I
不能只是扩展它，我没有办法
have to rewrite the whole data structure
必须重写整个数据结构
from scratch so in practice when you
从头开始，所以在实践中
face the scalability challenges in real
真正面对可扩展性挑战
life you almost always find that no
生活中，你几乎总是发现没有
existing controller solves your problem
现有的控制器可以解决您的问题
the way you want you still have to write
你想要的方式还是要写
it from scratch and again it doesn't
从头开始，它又一次没有
happen often because most of the damages
经常发生，因为大部分损害
write the code just works I mean in any
编写代码就可以了
type of complication most of the code
并发症类型大多数代码
just is not performance sensitive at all
只是对性能完全不敏感
there's at most one percent of your code
最多只有您代码的百分之一
that needs this attention to scalability
需要对可伸缩性的关注
performance and usually writing
表演和平时写作
something specifically if if again if
特别是如果再次
your business domain is where
您的业​​务领域在哪里
performance matters if you care bus
如果您在乎公车，性能很重要
codes if you want to analyze this real
代码，如果您想分析这个真实的
term big data work clothes then it's
术语大数据工作服，那么
usually pays off in writing in writing
通常以书面形式还清
your own customized invalidation
您自己的自定义无效
oh that's that's a really hard question
哦，那是一个非常困难的问题
I mean there's it it's a thriving area
我的意思是那里是一个繁荣的地区
of research and there's lots of our
研究，我们有很多
formal methods to produce those proof
产生这些证明的正式方法
the problem is all the formal methods
问题是所有形式上的方法
that first of all they don't scale to
首先，他们没有扩大规模
beacons complex algorithms the second
信标复杂算法第二
problem is like you write in some
问题就像你写一些
special language your code then you have
使用特殊语言编写代码
approval that would prove your code but
批准将证明您的代码，但
then the complex problem how you
那么复杂的问题你怎么
translate this proven algorithm into the
将此经过验证的算法转换为
actual code how you make sure you have
实际代码如何确保您拥有
not introduced any backs bugs while
没有引入任何背景错误
while making the switch so so what's
同时进行切换，所以这是什么
more a practical pragmatical question is
一个更实际的实用问题是
how do I test that is correct and for
我该如何测试正确和正确的
this purpose there was a bunch of
这个目的有一堆
framework sexually there is I don't have
性框架我没有
a link there is if you google for
如果您使用google链接
example there is link check to open
例子有链接检查打开
source ELISA for example check veneers
来源ELISA，例如检查单板
ability of your data structures and a
您的数据结构的能力和
multiple threads it's not it doesn't
多线程，不是，不是
prove you anything but it lets you
向您证明一切，但可以让您
quickly find common common bugs that you
快速找到您常见的常见错误
did and oh I'll prove is the work in the
做到了，我会证明这是
rest of us I've been I've been involved
我们其余的人我一直在参与
in its design you know and creation of
在其设计中，您知道并创造了
this tool so but not tools there is
这个工具，所以不是工具
nothing entry and that from you know
没什么，你知道的
design to unfortunately and that's still
设计不幸的是，这仍然
open question hopefully somebody solves
希望有人解决这个问题
it some point in the future
在未来的某个时候
yep
是的
it's a is Java if you if you replace the
如果您要替换的是Java
synchronized with whistling words my
与我的口哨声同步
sink right so you pee yeah you can
正确的下沉，所以你尿尿是的，你可以
replace synchronized with javis rented
替换与javis租用同步
lock you'll get approximately the same
锁你会得到大致相同
performance I mean because inside
性能我的意思是因为里面
they're very similar I mean it just
他们非常相似，我是说
synchronize it's just less code and with
同步，只需更少的代码
reinterred block actually in cotton
棉花中的再烧结块
there is a nice extension so you can do
有一个很好的扩展，所以你可以做
it with lock model so it's it's actually
它与锁模型，所以它实际上是
using interlocked is way more
使用互锁方式更多
comfortable in cotton because of the DSL
DSL使棉质穿着舒适
nature of cotton so you write much less
棉花的性质，所以你写的少得多
code because in Java just very very
代码，因为在Java中
broad boilerplate so in Java you would
广泛的样板，所以在Java中，
usually use synchronous just because
通常使用同步只是因为
using your entered Locker just produces
使用您输入的储物柜只会产生
lines and lights a boilerplate in cotton
线和点燃棉花样板
is not a big problem but from the
不是什么大问题，但从
scalability standpoint there is no win
可扩展性的观点没有成功
the reason why people would use rented
人们使用房租的原因
lock is totally different the reason why
锁是完全不同的原因
people would use your ended lock is if
人们会使用您的终止锁，如果
they want is they having very complex
他们想要的是他们非常复杂
data structure with lots of locks which
具有很多锁的数据结构
is a challenge to design because you
设计是一个挑战，因为您
have to make sure that you don't try to
必须确保您不要尝试
deadlock and they want to hand over
僵局，他们想移交
locking they want to take one lock but
锁定他们想要一把锁，但是
then another then it really is the first
然后另一个然后是真的
one there's no way you can do it with
一个没有办法可以做到
Java synchronized but with your
Java已同步但与您的
interlock you can do it because you can
可以互锁，因为您可以
control input your invitations of lock
控制输入​​您的锁定邀请
up and lock but from performance then
并锁定，但从性能开始
where there's there's no wind from skull
那里没有风
podium
讲台
yeah you can do we dreadlock in there is
是的，你可以做到的
there is approach yeah there is there's
有办法，是的，有
actually there is thing called to reach
其实有东西叫达到
dreadlock
辫子
so you can use a separate you can do
所以你可以单独使用
read lock but the the problem is do
读锁，但问题是
dreadlocks it's it's it's a source of
dreadlocks这是它的来源
over here so we still get this lock in
在这里，所以我们仍然可以锁定
over here even though you in crystal
即使你在水晶上
currency by dreadlocks it's another
dreadlocks货币，这是另一种
techniques
技术
so basically when you're running to
所以基本上当你跑到
sculpt with your problem since locks one
由于锁定一个而雕刻您的问题
thing is go lock free the others go read
事情是去锁自由，其他去读
read lock so there's two different
读锁，所以有两个不同
sometimes you know if it's data
有时候你知道是不是数据
structure is very complex it compensates
结构非常复杂，可以补偿
search a hard to implement lock for your
搜索难于实现的锁
way I mean I mean there's some limit on
我的意思是，我的意思是
how a complicated structure can be to
复杂的结构如何
make it lock free so usually the rule of
使其自由锁定，因此通常是
thumb of this if your structure is
如果您的结构是
simple enough so you can make it look
非常简单，因此您可以使其外观
for just make it lock free if you cannot
如果无法将其锁定，
make it for walk free then but you still
让它自由走走，但你仍然
have to scale and matzo first then you
必须先扩大规模，然后你
would go with ruh dreadlocks
会和ruh dreadlocks一起去